LUIZ FLÁVIO FELIZARDO

Software Engineer

State of Minas Gerais Brazil

+55 (35) 98857 5758

Email: dev felizardo@gmail.com

Portfolio: <u>devfel.com</u>
Github: <u>github.com/devfel</u>
Linkedin: <u>linkedin.com/in/devfel</u>

ABOUT ME

Hello, I'm Luiz Felizardo, I have started programming using QBasic language, back in 2003. After that first experience, I never stopped and fell in love with the technology field and computer science in general. I really enjoy learning, the pursuit of knowledge is my hobby.

SKILLS & INTERESTS

HTML CSS **JAVASCRIPT** REACT **BOOTSTRAP** GIT **GITHUB** JSON **VS CODE** MySQL MongoDB **PostgreSQL VUE** Node.JS Python BPM **BPMN Function Point Analysis UML SPSS**

EXPERIENCE

2013 – present (7+ years)

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Federal University of São João del-Rei

Selected to work as the IT analyst through a very competitive civil service examination by having the best grade among approximately 200 candidates.

The role in the university includes performing different tasks such as System development, support, software analysis, maintenance, and more.

Implementation, Mapping, Documentation, Training, and Support of several systems within the university administration field like warehouse, audit, internal control, scholarships, purchasing, contracts, invoices, budget, patrimony, protocol, transportation, and so on.

Another important role was the design and standardization of a new process model for software implementation using BPM and BPMN.

Jul 2017 – Dec 2017 (6 months)

SOFTWARE ENGINEER MANAGER

Federal University of São João del-Rei

Responsible for managing a team of 13 developers. The team upgraded and implemented several systems to handle various administrative and academic tasks at the University during this time.

Position acquired through voting among the team members and with the IT Director's endorsement.

Jul 2009 – present (11+ years)

Ph.D., MASTER'S & UNDERGRAD RESEARCHER

Federal University of Lavras / Federal University of Itajubá

Participation on the foundation of the "Black Bee Drones", the first academic team of intelligent drones of Latin America. The team obtained a 3^{rd} place prize in the 2015 IMAV competition held in Aachen, Germany, and a special achievement prize for the unexpectedly good result as first-time competitors.

More than 20 studies published on conference proceedings and journals in the areas of smart cities, systems to solve conflicts related to the use of water and other environmental issues, statistical discriminant analysis and crosstabulation, artificial intelligence, and unnamed aerial vehicles.

EDUCATION

2019 - present

DOCTORATE (Ph.D.) - Management & Administration

Federal University of Lavras

Courses and subjects needed already fulfilled, only the thesis is left.

2013 - 2014

MASTER (M.Sc.) - Computer Science & Technology

Federal University of Itajubá

Area: Computational Mathematics - Research Field: A.I.

2014 - 2014

POST-GRADUATION - Project Management MBA

Federal University of Itajubá

Field of Study: PMBOK Project Management Body of Knowledge, BPM & BPMN.

2006 - 2012

BACHELOR - COMPUTER SCIENCE

Federal University of Itajubá